Ogiso Private High School
Yuki Yokoya
I am Yuki Yokoya.
What?!
Please call me Yuki.
Apparently, she's Yokoya's cousin.
There's a seat open right in front of him,
so please be seated there.
She's so cute!
Seriously?
I look forward to taking classes
with you, Master Hitoyoshi.
What?! Master Hitoyoshi?!
Oh, man...
Ms. Yuki! Big Brother! How was school?
Ogiso Private High School
This was all your doing, wasn't it?
Nya-ha-ha! Consider yourself surprised!
Riko!
But, you know... Ms. Yuki really is amazing!
She's a lightning-fast learner!
I ran out of things to teach her
after three days!
Toward the end, she was even
doing my homework for me!
Right?
Miss Riko praised me so much that
I couldn't help but get a little carried away.
Oh, I see.
Wait, I still have a lot of questions!
Like, how did you transfer in?!
Where'd you pull the whole cousins thing from?
And why'd you say your last name is Yokoya?
Not to mention, how are you
in the same grade as me?!
And above all, why didn't you tell me
about any of this? Stuff like that!
I was able to transfer in by pulling a few
strings through my underground connections.
The cousins setup was suggested by Miss Riko.
She said I would be more easily accepted
if I claimed to be a relative.
And since I am now your cousin,
I borrowed the name Yokoya from you.
I think I am a little older than you,
but I thought being in the same grade
would better allow me to serve you.
And as for why I kept it all a secret,
that was because...
Miss Riko said it would be more fun this way.
Yay!
Riko...
Seriously, I can't believe you!
Ow!
Uh... Um.
Have I done something to upset you?
Oh, no, it's not that I'm angry,
more just... a little surprised.
Ah, well.
Let's enjoy a normal school life
together, Ms. Yuki.
Yes, let's!
Ogiso Private High School
Aw, yeah! It's finally time!
Katsuda Love
Here I come, Katsuda Bread!
Outta the way!
Episode 4: You Won't Miss Out.
Katsuda... Bread...
Ms. Yuki, what do you want to do for lunch?
I was thinking of going to the
convenience store, but...
Katsuda... Bread...
What?! You want Katsuda Bread?
But it's in such rare supply, you need to
dash for it the moment the bell rings...
Rare...
You see, the Katsuda Side
Dish Store closes early,
and there's no way for students
to make it there in time after school.
So instead, our school store serves a selection
of their bread-based items each Wednesday.
And the most popular one among them...
is yakisoba bread with plenty
of Katsuda's Sauce mixed inside,
commonly known as Katsuda Bread.
Personally, I'm more of a
Katsuda Sandwich fan, though.
Thing is, our classroom is the farthest one
from the school store,
Schoolyard
School Store
B Wing
A Wing
Pool
Gymnasium
so even if we leave now,
we'll never make it in time.
Katsuda... Bread...
Where is the school store?
Huh?
My mentor taught me something once.
"Even if your prey should strike you,
do not fail to take it down."
Please do not worry, Master Hitoyoshi.
I will obtain this Katsuda Bread without fail.
I shall return!
M-Ms. Yuki?!
Wait! Hold on, Ms. Yuki!
If you stand out too much...
we'll have a huge problem...
on our hands...
I let her go off on her own again...
No, I couldn't have stopped her.
There was no way I could.
Because...
Her face was...
the face of a girl in a dessert shop!
I know this all too well.
In the pursuit of delicious desserts,
the means, the effort, the cost—
none of that matters!
It's no exaggeration to say that a girl's true
potential is brought out in such moments!
What that means is...
If it's her desire and willpower to taste
Katsuda's Sauce that's driving her right now...
Katsuda's Sauce
None on this earth can stop her!
The concept of "normal" within Ms. Yuki
has veered off in an unexpected direction!
That's...
the first wave of the Katsuda Brigade!
Katsuda Love
No one asked me, but clever little Riko
is going to explain it to you anyway!
The Katsuda Brigade are those who,
captivated by the Katsuda Side Dish Store's
food, will travel any distance to seize it!
Katsuda Love
Katsuda! Katsuda!
They are soldiers who put their lives
on the line for Katsuda Bread,
training their leg strength and
sprinting ability each and every day!
What's more, their love for
Katsuda Bread runs so deep
that they perform a mysterious dance
while savoring its flavor!
This is bad! At this rate...
Ms. Yuki, who's about to drop in from above,
is going to clash with the Katsuda Brigade
right in front of the school store!
I can see the future, and it's not pretty!
She's leaping the distance?!
No way!
Though... This might actually...
Croquette Bread
Egg Sandwich
Sandwich
Yakisoba Bread
Katsu Sandwich
May I please have one Katsuda Bread
and one Katsuda Sandwich?
I can't possibly apologize enough.
They said the Katsuda Side Dish Store bread
is limited to one per person, so...
I'm fine with this croquette bread here!
Still...
Would you...
dine upon this?
No... Why don't you eat it?
Is it truly all right for me
to be the only one to do so?
Yeah, go ahead. I've had it before, anyway.
And you won it fair and square.
Then...
I was going to call out her outrageous
behavior from earlier, but...
When I see that blissful look on her face,
I can't bring myself to rain on her parade.
Master Hitoyoshi...
Please have this.
Huh?
That'd be... Um...
Please! There's no need to hold back.
Then... if you'll excuse me.
How is it?
It's very...
d-delicious.
Yokoya
Mochita, I'm sleeping over today!
Didn't you already visit a whole lot
during summer vacation?
What are you talking about?!
I know Ms. Yuki can do it with you
any night she wants, but...
Watch your wording!
This is a big deal for someone like me
who's been wanting
a big sister this whole time!
We can chat about fashion,
stay up all night talking about love,
secretly eat late-night snacks...
The possibilities are endless!
Just so you know, I wanted
a big sister so badly that...
at one point, I almost tried to trick myself
in believing you were my big sister instead!
Big Sister!
My dear Riko.
Who the heck?!
And you better rein in that wild imagination!
Anyway...
Clever little Riko just thought of an idea!
If you and Ms. Yuki got married,
everything would work out perfectly!
Why am I the one getting carried off?!
Huh? Cuz I prefer it that way.
You're honest, at least.
But if you ask me... I think Ms. Yuki is
in love with you, Big Brother! For sure!
Huh?!
Wait, wait. There's no way that's true.
I don't think she's into
romance in the first place.
Nuh-uh. Who do you think understands
a girl's heart better, you or me?
B-But... The other day...
she gave me some Katsuda Bread
with total innocence in her eyes.
There was nothing romantic about it.
You kidding me? That's so lovey-dovey! She's
gotta be this close to popping the question!
Got plans for the wedding?
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Hmm...
I know Mom would probably be okay with it,
but I dunno about Dad.
He's pretty stubborn, just like you.
In either case, I have no—
We should hold both Eastern-
and Western-style weddings!
Is someone getting married?
Oh, uh... No.
We were talking about how nice it would be
if you could become my big sister for real!
Riko!
You like my big brother, don't you, Ms. Yuki?
Riko, you little...
Yes, I admire him dearly.
Oh, Ms. Yuki! I want to eat a persimmon!
Could you please peel it for me?
Certainly.
Hey... I've been wondering
this for a while, but...
You don't usually wear makeup,
do you, Ms. Yuki?
Katsuda's Sauce
My apologies for my unsightly appearance.
During the day, I wear some
basic foundation, but...
What? Every girl dreams of being able
to look that good without makeup!
I wish I could look that cute, too!
Is that so?
I can't say I've found my appearance
to be of much benefit in the past.
That's a good point!
Beauty like yours, Ms. Yuki,
comes with its own share of troubles!
In my case, my face doesn't really stand out...
But when I grow older, I'm going to buy
lots of makeup and make myself cute!
I like your face, Miss Riko.
It's adorable, and expressive, and...
R-Really?
Yes.
That makes me happy.
I don't usually hear that from
people besides Mom and Dad.
Do you think I could become
as beautiful as you, Ms. Yuki?
Come to think of it,
ever since I discovered tonkatsu sauce...
I feel like my skin has become smoother.
What?!
If you'd like, please try it for yourself.
Is this actually good?
I think it brings out the sweetness.
Like when you put salt on watermelon?
You might have a point!
Oh! This works surprisingly well!
If you ask me, you guys
seem like sisters already.
I'm sure it's thanks to Riko that she was
able to adapt so easily into our daily life,
and it might be best
for girls to stick together.
Hey, Big Brother! I bet you just thought,
"If I marry Ms. Yuki in the future,
I'll be able to see this side of her every day,
won't I?" or something like that, right?
What?!
Marriage? I'm afraid I'm not
familiar with such things...
Please don't pressure me even harder!
In Japan, once Big Brother turns eighteen,
he can get married!
Then you can officially
become a Yokoya, Ms. Yuki!
Oh, is that so?
Don't put ideas in her head!
Wouldn't you be happy, too,
if you could have a bride like Ms. Yuki?
Huh?!
Just hypothetically!
Well... Y-Yeah, I guess...
Yay! He's committed now!
Riko?!
Ugh, just be quiet already!
All right!
Can't take it back now!
Ogiso Private High School
All right, quiet down!
"I am a cat,
but as yet I have no name."
"Where I was born is entirely unknown to me."
"But this still dimly lives in my memory."
That darn Riko barely
left us alone all weekend.
"I was mewing in a gloomy, damp place,
where I got the first sight
of a creature called man."
Now, thanks to that...
Basically, from the point of view
of an anthropomorphized cat,
it portrays the strangeness of things we
consider common sense in human society, and...
You there! Don't you dare fall asleep!
This wasn't what I intended!
The chalk... split in two?
My eyes... My eyes!
That can't be, right?
It was totally together, wasn't it?
My apologies!
Oww...
Infirmary
I told her it was strictly prohibited
to bring knives to school, but...
I wonder if she doesn't feel
at ease without them?
Excuse me!
I got chalk in my eye...
Oh, my, a new patient.
Huh? What happened to Nurse Maruyama?
I'm Nitta. I'll be filling in
as school nurse from today.
Nice to meet you.
So, what's wrong with your eye?
Um...
I got hit in both eyes by pieces of chalk.
A whole piece? In both eyes?
It's a long story.
I see.
If that's the case, could you please
sit on the bed right there?
Okay...
She's pretty mysterious
for a school nurse.
Is that pretty girl a friend of yours?
Or your girlfriend, even?
Huh?
The girl who wears a bell around her neck.
I just happened to see you two
arrive together this morning,
so I was a little curious about her.
Oh, do you mean Ms. Yuki?
Yeah, she's a friend of mine...
or, well, my cousin, actually.
Your cousin?!
Did I say something funny?
No, I was just thinking
how you look nothing alike.
Well, that's true.
But I'd say someone like you is more my type.
Huh? Th-Thank you very... much?
Seriously, you're like a small animal.
It doesn't seem like there's
any damage to your eyeballs.
Now, then...
Shall I check to see if there's
anything else wrong with you?
What?
My dear Hitoyoshi.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
You're so cute when you're frightened.
Where did all this come from?!
Even erotic manga have more
emotional buildup than this!
Don't worry.
Besides, how do you know my name?
I'm going to give you the
best first time ever...
Master Hitoyoshi!
Are your eyes all right?!
I came as quickly as I could
after class ended, but...
Make sure to wash your
hands and gargle!
Oh, Ms. Yuki! I was so scared!
Make sure to wash your
hands and gargle!
What happened, Master Hitoyoshi?
Oh, come on! That was just a joke.
A school nurse joke.
Think about the scar you're leaving
on this young boy's heart!
But you're so cute. You're like a hamster,
all nibbles and squeaks.
Seriously?!
Right? Don't you agree,
Ms. "Yuki"?
I'll give you some eye drops, just in case.
Come on over.
Please, no more weird "jokes," okay?!
Oh, look at you quiver.
You're so cute, I could eat you up!
That's exactly the kind of thing
I want you to stop doing!
Make sure to wash your
hands and gargle!
Huh?
Ms. Yuki... You, too? What's going on?
I don't get—
Please...
stay away from him.
What? Does that mean...
If you ask me... I think Ms. Yuki is
in love with you, Big Brother! For sure!
Wait, wait! Does this mean that...
Ms. Yuki is jealous?!
Well...
It doesn't seem like a serious injury,
but if the pain becomes severe,
please be sure to go see a doctor
as soon as possible, okay?
My dear Hitoyoshi... and Ms. Yuki.
M-Ms. Yuki?
Master Hitoyoshi.
Yesh?!
My apologies for earlier.
For suddenly pulling you in close like that...
W-Well, I guess it did surprise me a bit.
There is something
I must tell you, Master Hitoyoshi.
What?! Um, is that...
Big Brother   Big Brother   Big Brother   Big Brother   Big Brother
I-I haven't mentally prepared myself yet!
That woman from earlier...
She is in the same business as me.
There's no doubt she's an assassin.
What?!
And here I thought you were here on work.
I'll crush your little pretend family for you.